presto.com.au 2016-04-19

# Terms and Conditions | Presto | Presto

_Last Updated: 15th of May 2015_

Our privacy policy contains the following sections: 1\. Who are we? 2\. Our privacy policy 3\. Changes to our privacy policy and links 4\. What kinds of personal information do we collect and how? 5\. What information do we collect when you use our website or a Presto Service? 6\. Do you have to identify yourself when you use our website? 7\. Why do we collect the information and how do we use or disclose it? 8\. How can you request not to receive direct marketing? 9\. Who do we disclose your personal information to? 10\. Do we disclose your information overseas? 11\. How do we handle credit information? 12\. How do we hold your personal information and keep it secure? 13\. How can you seek access to, and correction of your information? 14\. How can you seek further information or complain about a breach of your privacy?

## 1 Who are we?

We respect your privacy and we strive to be clear about how we collect, use, disclose and store your personal information. This Privacy Policy sets out how we handle personal information that we collect about you through Presto Movies, Presto TV and Presto Entertainment as well as any other related products and/or services supplied by us and which you purchase, subscribe to, or use (the **_Presto Service_** ). In this Privacy Policy **we** , **us** , and **our** refers to Foxtel Management Pty Limited ( ** _Foxtel_** ) in its own right, as agent for the Foxtel Partnership (in respect of Presto Movies) and as agent for Presto TV Pty Limited (in respect of Presto TV), as described further below:  
\- **Presto Movies** is supplied by Foxtel as agent for the Foxtel Partnership. The **_Foxtel Partnership_** means the partnership between Sky Cable Pty Limited and Telstra Media Pty Limited. \- **Presto TV** is supplied by Foxtel as agent for Presto TV Pty Limited. Presto TV's shareholders are Foxtel and Seven Network (Operations) Limited ( ** _Seven_** ) (together the **_Presto TV Shareholders_** ). \- **Presto Entertainment** is a bundled service comprising Presto Movies and Presto TV, each as explained above.

## 2 Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect personal information, how we hold it, how we use it and to whom we disclose this information. It explains what information we may collect from you when you use our website, certain third party websites or a Presto Service. It also sets out how you may access and seek correction of your personal information or complain about a breach of your privacy. There are a small number of differences in the ways in which we disclose your personal information depending on whether you are a subscriber to Presto TV, Presto Movies or Presto Entertainment. We clearly identify these differences in the relevant parts of this Privacy Policy.

## 3 Changes to this Privacy Policy and Links

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time if our practices change and we recommend that you check back often for updates to our Privacy Policy. You can check the "effective date" posted at the top to see when our Privacy Policy was last updated. On our websites you may find links to other websites not operated by us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to them – always check the privacy policy of any other website you enter.

## 4 What kinds of personal information do we collect and how?

Personal information is any information or an opinion about an identified individual, or information from which an individual can be reasonably identified.

When you apply for a Presto Service we collect personal information about you. This enables us to connect you to your Presto Service, and allows us to provide and administer that service. This information may include but is not limited to: \- your name, \- date of birth, \- email address, \- phone number, \- post code, \- credit card or bank account information, \- personal identification numbers (PINs), and \- other information relevant to the provision or support by us, or use by you of your Presto Service.

We may also collect personal information from you when you use a Presto Service, enter into one of our competitions or otherwise interact with us (such as through a website, an application or through social media). This may include but is not limited to information such as: \- preference information, \- viewing habits, and \- other usage data.

Further information on the information we collect when you use our website or a Presto Service is set out in section 5 below.

We may also collect your personal information from third parties where you have agreed with them that your information may be disclosed.

## 5 What information do we collect when you use our website or a Presto Service?

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information regarding activity on our website and certain third party websites, such as: \- the number of visitors to the website; \- the date and time of those visits; \- the number of pages viewed, navigation patterns; and \- where relevant, websites visited before visiting that website.

We may also collect information when you use a Presto Service, such as your viewing habits as well as how you locate and watch content. This may include information on your most frequently watched shows and channels.

**How do we collect this information?**

On these websites, or on the Presto Service, your visits are associated with cookies, beacons and/or local storage data which are unique identifiers that we use to store information about your current and previous visits. Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, mobile phone or other device. Depending on the type of cookie, they may enable us to recognise you (or your device) across different websites, services, devices and/or browsing sessions. Beacons communicate information from your device to a server and can be embedded in online content, videos and emails and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your device, know when you have viewed particular content or determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon and the IP address of your device.

This information is collected by us, on our behalf by various website analytics companies, and, if you subscribe to Presto TV or Presto Entertainment, in certain circumstances by the Presto TV Shareholders. Where this information is collected directly from you by a Presto TV Shareholder, the Presto TV Shareholder will use that information in accordance with their own privacy policy

Information collected by cookies, beacons and local storage data does not usually identify you. However, if such information is capable of identifying you, that information will be personal information. For example if you subscribe to a Presto Service, we may link information about your viewing habits, website activity or usage with your account information. We will treat all personal information collected about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and this may include disclosing it to third parties as set out in section 10 below.

**Why do we collect this information?**

This information provides us with statistics that we can use to analyse and improve our websites and our products and services. We may also use browsing and viewing habits data to deliver targeted marketing, advertising and content on our websites and the Presto Service, as well as Presto advertising on third party sites, in each case relating to your preferences or interests.

**How to opt out of targeted online marketing and advertising?**

More information about how we use cookies, what information is collected by Presto and the Presto TV Shareholders, which third party sites we collect information from and how you can request not to receive targeted marketing and advertising from Presto and the Presto TV Shareholders is available on the Presto Privacy Page which is located a presto.com.au/privacy/optout/presto.

## 6 Do you have to identify yourself when you use our website?

If you log into our website you will have identified yourself. Where possible, we allow you to use a pseudonym when contributing to our website. If you wish to remain anonymous when you use our website, do not sign in to the website or provide any information which may identify you.

## 7 Why do we collect the information and how do we use or disclose it?

We collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information: \- to assess your application for a Presto Service; \- to connect you to, and provide, support and administer your Presto Service, including billing you, contacting you about your Presto Service, and resolving any disputes about your Presto Service; \- to provide you with recommendations about use of your Presto Service and to personalise your experience with us; \- to develop and enhance our products and services; \- to conduct research and to plan and develop our product and marketing strategies; \- to provide and operate our competitions, events and promotions; \- to promote and market products and services of ours and our partners (including targeted online advertising); and \- to comply with our legal obligations.

If you are a Presto Movies or Presto Entertainment subscriber, you acknowledge and agree that any personal information we collect about you may be disclosed to the Foxtel Partners for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Use of your personal information by the Foxtel Partners is subject to their privacy policies. Please see section 10 of this Policy for further information on how to request us not to disclose your personal information to the Foxtel Partners.

If you are a Presto TV or Presto Entertainment subscriber, you acknowledge and agree that any personal information we collect about you may be disclosed to the Presto TV Shareholders and their related bodies corporate and used by those organisations for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy including direct marketing to you unless you have requested that they do not provide you with direct marketing. Please see section 8 of this Policy for further information on how to opt out of receiving direct marketing communications.

## 8 How can you request not to receive direct marketing?

If you do not wish to receive direct marketing communications: \- from us about Presto; or \- from the Presto TV Shareholders,

please contact us at support@presto.com.au and/or GPO Box 99 Sydney NSW 2001. You can adjust your marketing preferences at any time by logging into your Presto Account at www.presto.com.au.

If you change your preferences, it may take some time for this change to take effect. Within this time, you may still receive direct marketing, however we will ensure that your preferences are updated as promptly as possible.

## 9 What happens if I don’t allow you to use my personal information for direct marketing purposes?

You can still use and access the Presto Service even if you do not allow us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes. Please see section 8 of this Policy for further information on how to opt out of receiving such direct marketing communications.

If you do permit us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes we use your personal information to ensure that we can talk to you about ways to enhance your Presto Service, how to find the content you like, tell you about new services and applications and give you access to offers that we think will help you get the most out of your Presto Service. We will also use the information to provide you with access to exclusive experiences that are linked to your preferences.

## 10 Who do we disclose your personal information to and why?

**All users of the Presto Service**

We may disclose your personal information to: \- entities who assist us in providing, administering, supporting, improving, promoting and marketing our products and services and our competitions, events and promotions, including suppliers, contractors, website hosting service providers, debt collectors, data storage and management companies including providers of cloud services, channel providers, and interactive advertisers; \- companies that promote and market, or conduct research to help us improve and target, our products and services; \- where required by law, or to government and enforcement agencies or individuals appointed by a government responsible for investigating and resolving disputes or complaints concerning your Presto Service; and \- for other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

When you enter into a competition we are running or participate in a sponsored event, we may seek, as a condition of entry, consent to pass your information to a promoter or sponsor of the competition or event. If we do this, we will notify you at the time of entering into the competition or event with us.

**Subscribers to Presto Movies and Presto Entertainment**

If you have registered for Presto Movies or Presto Entertainment, we may also provide your personal information to the Foxtel Partners (News Australia Pty Limited and Telstra Media Pty Limited, and any of their related bodies corporate) who will use it for similar purposes as us. Use of your personal information by the Foxtel Partners is subject to their privacy policies.

If you do not wish us to provide your personal information to the Foxtel Partners, please contact us at support@presto.com.au and/or at GPO Box 99, Sydney, NSW 2001. You can adjust this preference at any time by logging into your Presto Account at www.presto.com.au.

**Subscribers to Presto TV and Presto Entertainment**

If you have registered for Presto TV or Presto Entertainment then we will disclose your personal information to the Presto TV Shareholders, which at the date of this policy are Foxtel and Seven. The Presto TV Shareholders will use your personal information for the purpose of: \- matching your data against other information held by them and their related bodies corporate; and \- performing analytics and reporting on an aggregate basis (but not to the public).

The Presto TV Shareholders and their related bodies corporate may also use your personal information for promotional and marketing purposes. By registering for Presto TV or Presto Entertainment, you consent to the Presto TV Shareholders and their related bodies corporate: \- sending direct marketing to you; and/or \- sending you targeted online advertising.

Use of your personal information by the Presto TV Shareholders and their related bodies corporate is subject to their privacy policies.

Please see section 8 of this Policy for further information on how to opt out of receiving such direct marketing communications.

More information on how to opt out of targeted online marketing and online advertising is available on the Presto Privacy Page which is located at www.presto.com.au/privacy/optout/presto.

If you have only subscribed to Presto Movies, we will not disclose your personal information to the Presto TV Shareholders.

## 11 Do we disclose your personal information overseas?

We may disclose your personal information to third parties overseas who provide services to us, including to our outsourced billing service providers located in the USA and the United Kingdom. We take reasonable steps necessary to ensure that these overseas recipients do not breach the Privacy Act.

We may also disclose your personal information overseas where a partner or sponsor of a competition or event we are running is located overseas. The countries where they are located vary. If we do this, we will notify you at the time of entering into the competition or event with us.

## 12 How do we handle credit information?

In certain very limited circumstances we may be a credit provider to you. In these circumstances, the identification information we collect about you (your name, date of birth and address) is also “credit information” (as defined in the Privacy Act). We do not collect credit information from, or disclose it to, any credit reporting bodies.

We will handle your identification information that is credit information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In particular, please refer to the following sections: 4\. What kinds of personal information do we collect and how? 7\. Why do we collect the information and how do we use or disclose it? 10\. Do we disclose your information overseas? 13\. How can you seek access to, and correction of your information? 14\. How can you seek further information or complain about a breach of your privacy?

## 13 How do we hold your personal information and keep it secure?

We hold your personal information in a combination of electronic and hard copy files. We may store your personal information with a third party data storage provider.

We may combine personal information we receive about you with other information we hold about you. This includes information received from third parties.

We take all reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we hold is protected from misuse, interference and loss, and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure by the use of various methods, including secure storage. Where we store your personal information with a third party data storage provider, we require them to keep it secure and only use or disclose it for the purpose for which it was provided.

Please contact us immediately if you become aware or have reason to believe there has been any unauthorised use of your personal information that we hold.

## 14 How can you seek access to, and correction of, your personal information?

If you would like to find out what information we have about you, please contact us at support@presto.com.au and/or at GPO Box 99, Sydney, NSW 2001. We will ask that you put your request for access in writing and provide us with proof of your identity. You may be charged an administration fee when we provide you with the requested information to cover our time and postage and handling or retrieval costs.

We will generally provide you with access to your personal information that we have about you, but sometimes that will not be possible, in which case we will give you a written notice explaining why.

If you think that any personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete, out-of-date or irrelevant, you may ask us to correct it. We will take reasonable steps to correct it unless we disagree with your reasons. If we refuse to correct your personal information we will give you a written explanation.

## 15 How can you access further information or complain about a breach of your privacy?

If you believe that we have breached your privacy or have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at support@presto.com.au or at GPO Box 99, Sydney, NSW 2001, or write to the Foxtel Privacy Officer at PO Box 612, Moonee Ponds, Victoria, 3039.

We will investigate any complaint, and notify you of our decision in relation to the complaint, as soon as practicable after it is received. If we are unable to satisfactorily resolve your concerns about our handling of your personal information, you can contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.
